Yes, gate C
Yes, the gate opens in 15 minutes,
and the plane departs in 45.
Ok, I will tell youuuu... I will tell you when I am on the plane. All right?
Bye-
As you can probably tell by the background noise,
I am at the airport,
I hope it doesn't bother us, because
I am going to take advantage of it, and show you what's in my suitcase.
But before getting started, this is my airport outfit,
in the airport outfit, what's key is:
wearing what takes up the most space,
Which is why here I have my jacket.
Trousers,
and yes, I am wearing this because if not I will roast in here.
[pause because I admit I talked really fast]
It's so hot here at the airport, I can't even,
lets see if they turn on the air conditioning please.
All right,
starting here,
maybe you are wondering:
why does she have a backpack inside a suitcase?
well, this is a hack, because
I had quite a few electronic devices,
and I placed them inside the backpack,
so that when I go though the security check,
I just get out this backpack,
and,
it's faster this way.
Once we are done with the backpack, before we had this notebook here,
honestly, I haven't used it at all,
BUT, it's a very cool notebook,
because I made it myself.
It's like this, with a japanese bookbinding.
Isn't it cool?
Look: ASMR
It's a notebook I made myself and that's it.
Up next we have this third bag,
the smaller, the better.
That is my rule, because that means that you take less with you.
And the less you take, the better.
This is called 'riñonera'.
It's worn by a lot, a lot of people in Spain,
There is nothing better than finding money inside bags.
Up next, right here,
I have a huge gap:
I have a gap... I mean...
Here is the usual clothing level,
and here I have a huge gap because here is where the tripod goes.
And so inside the tripod (gaps) I put in my toothbrush,
which is made out of wood.
I have this other brush, that I use for my body, to clean myself
to shower.
And here I have something that is not what it looks like,
not everything is what it looks like.
Because here it says sunscreen,
but it's not sunscreen.
This is shampoo.
So when I go shower, I put it on my head.
Why is it in this container?
Because... Where is it? Ah!
Because this container is only 100millimeters,
and 100ml is what they allow in the hand luggage.
Because this is my hand luggage, I am not checking in.
Check in is when you pay,
and they put your suitcase in the trunk of the plane.
[in english the joke makes no sense lol]
Suitcase, trunk.
And when you land, the suitcase comes out through the belt,
that which I think is super cool,
the conveyor belt,
and it starts spinning around,
and you have to wait for your suitcase to reach you.
But I am not going to do that.
I also have this hair brush,
I don't brush my hair a lot
because if I do, it looks like I have been tased,
It goes:
And then we have the clothes;
If I am being honest with you, I haven't used half of it,
but I brought it just in case, because I didn't know,
with the whole global pandemic,
I didn't know when I would be able to go back,
So basically I packed all clothes,
that will last me...
Till' the infinity and beyond-
That lasts me until the arrival of the cold season.
So that means that I could be... pft
If the whole year was summer time,
I would be able to live with this suitcase, pft
enough, more than enough,
because I brought things that I still haven't used:
These pants,
it's the first time I use them, I haven't used them at all.
And then we have these other pants
that I also haven't used at all...
these that I did use,
these that I used one time,
and these that I use every day:
when these pants get dirty, I wear this skirt.
And then here I have a dress someone gifted me:
it's nice, to go to the beach and stuff.
Tank top,
crop tops and then these:
Were made by my grandma with the sewing machine-
Here it is, the sewing machine.
-with another dress that was also gifted to me,
but that I didn't like.
And she made this top for me, and it's verY cute. It's super cute.
Doesn't it look good?
I already knew it.
Now, the key to packing a suitcase,
it's in knowing how to fold the clothes,
and knowing how to pack it.
In videogames, each character has a special ability:
well then, the special ability of my lineage, of my family,
is packing suitcases.
The trick is in filling in the gaps, the little gaps.
-like in tetris-
Shoes: these are the ones I am wearing right now.
The other day I fell a couple times,
because the shoes no longer have...
I have...
They are the only shoes I wear in winter,
and so they are worn away.
The sole, this is the sole,
the sole is flat.
It no longer has any roughness, so it no longer grips well onto the floor,
so the other day I was walking on the mountain, and
I slid and fell, and have a couple bruises.
Here we have bruise Nº1, in it we can distinguish 3 colors:
Green, purple and yellow.
And here we have bruise Nº2, in which we can notice the:
sliding: of my ass against the floor,
and of my leg against a plant.
So these are the shoes that I use in winter
and in summertime when I go on a hike or walking,
and these are the shoes that I use in summertime
...I won't show them too much because they are kind of dirty.
aAnd if my mother watches this video she is going to tell me off for not washing them.
Attention, last call:
Always the same thing!